https://www.adversus.com/adversus-privacy-policy-and-cookies/

Skip to content
Menu FASHION
FASHION FALL WINTER 2019 2020FASHION SPRING SUMMER 2020Fashion Summer 2019Fashion ShowsNo commentBEAUTYMODELS
FASHION MODELSSTYLE
VIDEO
Menu FEATURED MODELSBEAUTYFASHIONSTYLEACADEMICA
Menu FASHION
FASHION FALL WINTER 2019 2020FASHION SPRING SUMMER 2020Fashion Summer 2019Fashion ShowsNo commentBEAUTYMODELS
FASHION MODELSSTYLE
VIDEO
ADVERSUS. COM does not actively collect any personal data.Google AnalyticsWe use Google Analytics in order to know how many people read our sites. This is the only information we need, for this reason we disable every possible function we could disable from our Google Analytics control panel, and added the following string to our Google Analytics tag gtag(‘config’, ‘<GA_TRACKING_ID>’, { ‘anonymize_ip’: true }); in order to anonymize our readers ip address.Non-personalized Google AdsenseGoogle Adsense banners are displayed on the pages of ADVERSUSTo guarantee your privacy we have opted for the NON-personalized ads. Non-personalized ads should not collect any personal data. Google writes:‘Non-Personalized ads will use only contextual information, including coarse general (city-level) location, and content on the current site or app; targeting is not based on the profile or past behavior of a user.‘ Source GoogleTo read more about the Google Adsense and the Google Adsense privacy policy:
https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sitesContacting usWe do not use any contact form. Contact forms can sometimes collect personal information such as Ip addresses, so we decided to not use them. If you want to contact us, you can use our ‘traditional’ email address press (at) adversus.com – Replace (at) with @.Cookies policyA cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.Adversus.com does not use any cookies to collect any personal data. To make our website function we need to use programs as WordPress. These third parties use cookies to be able to make our website function (WordPress).Changes privacy/cookies statementWe reserve the right to change this privacy statement. Changes will be published on this website.SEARCH ON ADVERSUS
Search for:
LATEST ON ADVERSUS
ACADEMICAADVERSUS COVER MODELSBEAUTYCARSFASHIONHOW LOW CAN YOU GOSTYLESupermodelsTRAVELVIDEO
Close
